‘Senator’, we're making
our ‘final’ approach into ‘Coruscant’.
“Senator”, we're making
our “final” approach into “Coruscant”.
''Senator'', ''we'''re making
our ''final'' approach into ''Coruscant''.
now / only ask,
| can only ask. So do /
/t shouldn't be you. |t should be me.
1 haven't done that.
And if l refuse?
-Francine, what happened?
-I don't know. You should tell me!
- Do you believe him?
- (KNOCK AT DOOR)
Do you believe him?
- (SNICKERS)
- Do you believe him?
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
Do you believe him?
(SNICKERS)
- (SNICKERS)
- Do you believe him?
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
- (SNICKERS)
Do you believe him?
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
(WHISPERS) I've never done this
with the power so low before.
(KNOCK AT DOOR) It's okay. I'm with you.
(CLEARS THROAT) But you don't
need to be a nuclear scientist
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
- LEGASOV K: At 28 minutes past midnight,
(GRUNTS SOFTLY)
(KNOCK AT DOOR)
(SIGHS)
("WHEN I'M CALLING YOU" PLAYING ON RADIO)
[German]
STEPASHIN: Comrade Khomyuk.
MAN 1: A beauty from beyond the Wall.
MAN 1: Oh, if you were my girl,
I wouldn't leave you alone.
- BRANT: Right.
- (GILLY CRYING)
DEREK: Turn her over.
BRANT: All right.
- Valar Morghulis.
- ALL: Valar Dohaeris.
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
Subtitles by FooBar
Foo     bar.
"FooBar"  ...
...
Ahhhh?!?
Ohhh.
Huuummm
Hey!!
NARRATOR: Previously on 11.22.63...
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
- | forget everything when I'm reading.
- "From Here to Eternity."
HARRY: The day that changed my life.
♪ That old black magic ♪
♪ That you, uh, weave so well ♪
- ♪ Those icy fingers ♪
- Cigars? Cigarettes?
VARYS: Cersei controls fewer than
half the Seven Kingdoms.
- (ALL APPLAUDING)
(BELL RINGS)
- Can you write a letter to the principal?
(CHUCKLES)
CHRISTY: Hi.
AL: How are you?
AL: Get out of here. (CONTINUES COUGHING)
(IN ENGLISH) "The prince who was
promised will bring the dawn."
- MAN: (ON TV) In the 1930s...
(CHUCKLES)
LITTLEFINGER:
I delivered his bones myself.
iSubDB.com - fast, modern, simple
Subtitles search by drag & drop